<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Star Love</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string-array name="rate_options">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
    </string-array>
    


    <string name="boba_name">Boba Fett</string>
    <string name="boba_about">With his customized Mandalorian armor, deadly weaponry, 
        and silent demeanor, Boba Fett was one of the most feared bounty hunters in the 
        galaxy. A genetic clone of his “father,” bounty hunter Jango Fett, Boba learned 
        combat and martial skills from a young age. Over the course of his career, which 
        included contracts for the Empire and the criminal underworld, he became a legend.
    </string>
    <string name="boba_location">Kamino</string>
    <string name="boba_gender">Male</string>
    <string name="boba_height">1.83 m</string>
    <string name="boba_lookingfor">A goodlooking bounty huntress.</string>



    <string name="c3po_name">C-3PO</string>
    <string name="c3po_about">C-3PO is a droid programmed for etiquette and protocol,
        built by the heroic Jedi Anakin Skywalker, and a constant companion to astromech
        R2-D2. Over the years, he was involved in some of the galaxy’s most defining moments
        and thrilling battles -- and is fluent in over six million forms of communication.
    </string>
    <string name="c3po_location">Tatooine</string>
    <string name="c3po_gender">Protocol Droid</string>
    <string name="c3po_height">1.67 m</string>
    <string name="c3po_lookingfor">Someone like R2D2, but more sexy.</string>



    <string name="chewie_name">Chewbacca</string>
    <string name="chewie_about">A legendary Wookiee warrior and Han Solo’s co-pilot aboard
        the Millennium Falcon, Chewbacca was part of a core group of Rebels who restored
        freedom to the galaxy. Known for his short temper and accuracy with a bowcaster,
        Chewie also has a big heart -- and is unwavering in his loyalty to his friends.
    </string>
    <string name="chewie_location">Kashyyyk</string>
    <string name="chewie_gender">Male</string>
    <string name="chewie_height">2.28 m</string>
    <string name="chewie_lookingfor">Someone who doesn't mind all the hair.</string>



    <string name="leia_name">Princess Leia Organa</string>
    <string name="leia_about">Princess Leia Organa was one of the Rebel Alliance’s greatest
        leaders, fearless on the battlefield and dedicated to ending the tyranny of the Empire.
        Daughter of Padmé Amidala and Anakin Skywalker, sister of Luke Skywalker, and with
        a soft spot for scoundrels, Leia ranks among the galaxy’s great heroes.
    </string>
    <string name="leia_location">Alderaan</string>
    <string name="leia_gender">Female</string>
    <string name="leia_height">1.50 m</string>
    <string name="leia_lookingfor">A guy that is not my brother and neither a fat slug
        like Jabba the Hutt.</string>



    <string name="vader_name">Darth Vader</string>
    <string name="vader_about">Once a heroic Jedi Knight, Darth Vader was seduced by the
        dark side of the Force, became a Sith Lord, and led the Empire’s eradication of the
        Jedi Order. He remained in service of the Emperor -- the evil Darth Sidious -- for
        decades, enforcing his Master’s will and seeking to crush the fledgling Rebel Alliance.
        But there was still good in him…
    </string>
    <string name="vader_location">Death Star</string>
    <string name="vader_gender">Male</string>
    <string name="vader_height">2.03 m</string>
    <string name="vader_lookingfor">People to join the dark side.</string>



    <string name="padme_name">Padmé Amidala</string>
    <string name="padme_about">Padmé Amidala was a courageous, hopeful leader, serving as
        Queen and then Senator of Naboo -- and was also handy with a blaster. Despite her
        ideals and all she did for the cause of peace, her secret, forbidden marriage to Jedi
        Anakin Skywalker would prove to have dire consequences for the galaxy.
    </string>
    <string name="padme_location">Naboo</string>
    <string name="padme_gender">Female</string>
    <string name="padme_height">1.65 m</string>
    <string name="padme_lookingfor">A brave Jedi.</string>



</resources>
